IntelliJ IDEA has powerful refactoring capabilities.
IntelliJ IDEA具有强大的重构功能。
In this screencast, we'll cover why, when and how to apply the Inline Method refactoring
在此截屏视频中，我们将介绍为什么，何时以及如何应用内联方法重构
and how IntelliJ IDEA can help you get started.
以及IntelliJ IDEA如何帮助您入门。
The idea of Inline Refactoring is simple.
内联重构的思想很简单。
Just replace a method call with its contents.
只需将方法调用替换为其内容即可。
In IntelliJ IDEA, you can either select a method name or place your cursor at the start/
在IntelliJ IDEA中，您可以选择方法名称，也可以将光标置于开始/
end/ middle of a method name.
方法名称的结尾/中间。
Use the 'Inline Method' from the menu.
使用菜单中的“内联方法”。
Or you can also use the shortcut Alt+Ctrl+N on Windows/ Linux and Option+Command+N on
或者，您也可以在Windows / Linux上使用快捷键Alt + Ctrl + N，在Windows上使用Option + Command + N
macOS.
苹果系统。
IntelliJ IDEA gives you the option of deleting or keeping the method, after you inline its
内联后，IntelliJ IDEA使您可以选择删除或保留该方法
contents.
内容。
For this example, we'll delete the method.
对于此示例，我们将删除该方法。
But why would you want to inline your methods?
但是，为什么要内联方法呢？
Let's work with a few use use cases.
让我们处理一些用例。
When a method call disrupts the flow in your code rather than simplifying it, you can consider
当方法调用破坏代码流而不是简化代码流时，您可以考虑
applying Inline Method.
应用内联方法。
In this code, call to the method compareRatingWithMethodParameter() is inserting unnecessary indirection in the
在此代码中，对方法compareRatingWithMethodParameter（）的调用将不必要的间接插入
method scheduleSession().
方法scheduleSession（）。
This code can be simplified by inlining the method compareRatingWithMethodParameter().
可以通过内联方法compareRatingWithMethodParameter（）来简化此代码。
However, you don’t have to inline every method that defines just one line of code.
但是，您不必内联所有仅定义一行代码的方法。
The decision should depend on whether it is helping you to understand the flow in your
该决定应取决于它是否有助于您了解自己的流程。
method.
方法。
When migrating your code to a later Java version, you may want to inline a couple of methods
在将代码迁移到更高的Java版本时，您可能需要内联一些方法
so that you can modify it together.
以便您可以一起修改它。
In this example, lets inline these two methods and then see how we could further refactor
在此示例中，让我们内联这两种方法，然后查看如何进一步重构
this code.
此代码。
Let's start by inlining method sortSpeakerNames.
让我们从内联方法sortSpeakerNames开始。
You can see the shortcuts at the bottom of the screencast.
您可以在截屏视频的底部看到快捷方式。
Now lets inline the method extractNamesFromSpeakerList().
现在，内联方法extractNamesFromSpeakerList（）。
Time to apply IntelliJ IDEA's magic.
是时候应用IntelliJ IDEA的魔力了。
Let's start by converting for loop to a stream.
让我们首先将for循环转换为流。
By using Alt+Enter you can invoke context actions in your code - which suggest what
通过使用Alt + Enter，您可以在代码中调用上下文操作-这将建议
you could do with a code construct.
您可以使用代码构造。
Now, I'll jump to the next errors/ suggestions by IntelliJ IDEA by using F2 and then using
现在，我将使用F2然后使用IntelliJ IDEA跳转到下一个错误/建议
Alt+Enter to view the available suggestions.
Alt + Enter查看可用的建议。
You can use this combination to remove unused imports, get suggestions on stream operations,
您可以使用此组合删除未使用的导入，获取有关流操作的建议，
remove redundant local variables and much more.
删除多余的局部变量等等。
Often you might see a piece of code, which is refactored poorly.
通常，您可能会看到一段代码，其重构能力很差。
Code in this method calls another method almost on all lines.
此方法中的代码几乎在所有行上都调用另一个方法。
Though it is readable, let's see if we could inline these methods and refactor it again
虽然可读，但让我们看看是否可以内联这些方法并再次进行重构
to improve the intent of the code.
改善代码的意图。
Let's start by inlining methods outputTrackName and the other method outputSpeakerList.
让我们先内联方法outputTrackName和另一个方法outputSpeakerList。
Since both these methods were used to output paramater values, let's extract them to a
由于这两种方法都用于输出参数值，因此我们将它们提取到
single method by using Extract Method Refactoring.
使用提取方法重构的单个方法。
Now, let's inline the other two methods - filterSpeakersWithoutTracks and findSpeakerSpeakingOnTrack.
现在，让我们内联其他两个方法-filterSpeakersWithoutTracks和findSpeakerSpeakingOnTrack。
Now, lets remove an intermediate collect and join both streams together.
现在，让我们删除一个中间收集并将两个流连接在一起。
By using Alt+Enter on the filter method, you get an option of merging filter chain on streams.
通过在过滤器方法上使用Alt + Enter，您可以选择合并流上的过滤器链。
By using F2, you can navigate to the next error, which states that local variable panelists
通过使用F2，您可以导航到下一个错误，该错误指出本地变量专门小组成员
is redundant.
是多余的。
Use Alt+Enter to inline variable.
使用Alt + Enter内联变量。
IntelliJ IDEA 2019.2 includes significant improvements to the Inline Method refactoring.
IntelliJ IDEA 2019.2对内联方法重构进行了重大改进。
A method might include multiple exit points by defining multiple return statements.
一个方法可以通过定义多个return语句来包括多个出口点。
When you inline such method in IntelliJ IDEA 2019.2, it can be modified to define just
在IntelliJ IDEA 2019.2中内联这种方法时，可以对其进行修改以仅定义
one exit point in the form of a single return statement.
一个出口，以单个return语句的形式存在。
IntelliJ IDEA refers to this feature as ‘transforms to single exit point’.
IntelliJ IDEA将此功能称为“转换为单个出口点”。
With the enhancements in IntelliJ IDEA 2019.2, the Inline Method refactoring also supports
通过IntelliJ IDEA 2019.2中的增强功能，内联方法重构也支持
negation at call site.
否定呼叫站点。
In this code, when you inline the method check() with negation, it won’t be modified to a
在这段代码中，当您将方法check（）内联为负数时，它将不会被修改为
‘single exit point’.
“单个出口点”。
Before we inline this method, note the return values.
内联此方法之前，请注意返回值。
It returns a false here, a false here, and the result of this expression here.
它在此处返回false，在此处返回false，并在此处返回此表达式的结果。
Let's inline this method.
让我们内联此方法。
See how the inlined code is negated – notice the reversal of return values (from false
查看内联代码如何取反-注意返回值的反转（从false
to true) and the condition (from equal to, To not equal to).
为true）和条件（从等于到，不等于）。
As developers, we refactor our code often.
作为开发人员，我们经常重构代码。
To refactor efficiently, we must know the use cases – why, when, and how to refactor
为了有效地重构，我们必须知道用例-为什么，何时以及如何重构
it.
它。
IntelliJ IDEA plays a crucial role by automating the various refactoring options for you.
IntelliJ IDEA通过自动为您提供各种重构选项起着至关重要的作用。
Thanks for watching.
感谢收看。